I'm super strong, super strong, super strong
tends to be successful
car
Elaine
The lock screen you made
I'm happy but don't be shy
Hey Masmat
Say it's super cute
Tell me you're the cutest
say something
As much as I was pampered
Become super cute
Because it will be the cutest
Choose whether you want to see or reflect the dark atmosphere
Even if I say it selfishly
I can't believe it's cute
Super strong super strong super strongest
You can do your best for me
Will this time be the best ever?
It's better than just comments Upper
Even pressure reppers have a word.
So, because of the public criticism, I'm half-chinned today.
It looks like she's going to be wearing a lot of costumes, so I'll make her look half-chinned.
I have some photos posted. that's why.
But there was something in the dressing room that I received from someone involved yesterday, so I looked at it again.
Make it half-chin.
Ah, I laughed.
What's the difference?
This is Gyokuro.
This is matcha. Matcha number one.
So, Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro Gyokuro
Right?
I thought so!
No, I don't think so
We're still in the same grade though
a!
Then name the cherry blossoms
Then my
Hey!
get over it
Yes, come!
Yes, the second day of Stapa begins here.
This is Nanoha-chan.
This is Nanoha. This is Nanoha.
This is Nanoha Aoyama from the union.
please.
A long time ago, when Star Parafes was released on YouTube, it was really small.
Do you remember? Do you remember?
It's gotten really, really big.
I can't speak at all, I'm not saying anything.
It's gotten bigger.
Seriously?
She's like a big sister to me, and I look up to her as a senior.
No, no, please stop.
I really liked him, and he sang to me, and I really liked him.
This time, the second part is MVTI.
that's right.
Yeah, why MVTI?
I feel confident.
Oh, that's amazing.
People say that I don't look very good.
Is that so?
They say it's good.
I'm an adventurer.
Is that so?
but.
Even when it comes to the members, I feel like, uh, there's something wrong with their personalities. Ah, certainly.
yes. Yes, there is. That's difficult. difficult.
Does it change every day? Oh, yes. It changes a lot. I change to do it every time.
Is that so? I've always been the main character. Eh! That's cool. I've always been the main character.
It just felt a little different. So, day two.
I want to do my best. thank you. I'm happy to see you. thank you.
thank you. see you.
Thank you for watching
Ah, dream influences also
me
dare
ni
yellow
There are 3
ani 6
congratulations
to the fans
sunly
Yay
4 hours today
NBTI is the same for 3 people in 4 hours
Congratulations
thank you
It was fun
It was a bit much
thank you
Boss festival impossible
That's right, isn't it?
I'm happy
yes
Choose Singalong Singathon
Because he's the main character
ENFJ
Singalong Singathon
I'm happy because there are so many members.
I took a video yesterday
50,000 pieces
Gather with the main characters
I wonder if it was used
Next is this video
Singalong Singathon has ended
Next
It's very amateurish
Very matchy Get some
fast forward
I am concerned with the eyes of the live-colored stadis.
He stayed in close contact with me for two days.
I wonder if viewership is going up?
I think there were 300,000 people?
That's right!
300,000 people came!
thank you
It's increasing more and more
People who eat Yakiniku also eat it.
pizza
Do you want to eat pizza?
I was enjoying it
Yay
But.
Even if you choose
Autumn sports let's all move our bodies
Mekimeki Daiso Contest
with Monoira Klauber
The entire thing was carried out
Yay
Hey, thanks for posting it.
Thank you very much everyone
thank you
This time is a stopmeki contest
We will hold an award ceremony
Yay
First, we will announce the individual awards.
yes
Stopmeki Contest
Who won the individual award
Super Tokimeki Advertising Department
This is Hiyori Yoshikawa
Click here for awards
amazing
altretter bark gift certificate
100,000 yen worth
That's nice
Wow, he's a really nice guy
He was such a nice guy
Hiyori
Individual award
By saying yes
congratulations
thank you
I danced in my room
Then mom
Tell me not to make any loud noises from above.
I was doing it more and more
Well, it was worth shaking the house more and more.
100,000 yen worth
thank you
No, it's amazing
That's 100,000 yen worth.
Is there anything you would like to buy?
home~~~
Too bad, the members are coming over.
Hahahaha
But even if everyone shares it
I agree
Yay!
congratulations!
I will applaud even louder today!
Hey, I'm happy
Unexpectedly
100,000 yen!
What should I buy?
I think he's the richest
Everyone isn't listening, right?
Because everyone was watching
Because everyone saw it
Because we played every day
But actually that video
That video
That video on TikTok now has about 30,000 likes.
My manager suddenly told me this while I was shopping at the supermarket.
Kyuu-chan, I suddenly got a call asking, “Do you want to eat exciting gymnastics now?”
Oh, I had something to say, so I lied and said I'd eat right away.
That's why my hard work was stolen
great
good
Give me that answer.
You're sweating so much
Because it's nothing
From that video too
congratulations
нед Well, I can't say it.
Masu
me
th
charm
Oh no, it's no good if you show up in a place like this.
Oh no, talk.
appeal.
I love Tanamin-chan.
For the time being, it would be best to stop posting content about advertising members.
He told me a lot that he loved Tokisen.
Tokisen-san became a commercial drama.
Also, I asked Yuuno to come along with me.
Is it okay?
Don't have a microphone?
On the viewing side, on the reflected side
Let's go
Ah, Tokisen's YouTube
let's talk
I wanted to talk to you before when KANAMI was there.
gresh tv
Change together again
different from yesterday
It's also pink
That's right
I
I remember this name
It's a plover, isn't it?
Quite famous
Lately I've been in the morning
Are you going to check this?
What does it mean?
What should I do to miss you?
I guess I need to change myself more after all.
That's what I thought though
I guess I should just tell you about mine.
So it's about to change
I hope I can meet you
How about me like this?
Do you think it's just cute?
I want you to keep looking at me
Please blink your eyes
12 minutes Last day
It's going to be the final, so I want to do my best to show all the parts I've been practicing so far. I think so.
I'm really working on voice care right now, and I'll do my best.
I also applied nervous eyelashes.
all eight
Oh no, I'm the most nervous during the 3rd minute.
What will happen?
it's okay
thank you
thank you for your hard work
Are you going to take a look?
yes
I wish you the best
Thank you for watching
thank you
It hasn't changed much, but I did have my hair braided here.
Everyone changes their hairstyle quite a lot.
These are the people who will be the top batters.
congratulations.
I'm now at the top
Is it cute?
I got dumped by you and became the best
That's a girl's reverse look
just tell me a little bit
If you said that, sure
Why are you disappointed?
I'm glad we broke up
I wanted you to think
Because I liked it
It's like we're at the same school
I feel like I'm going to be like Takuyo too
be in class
Yes, let's start
I'm bothering you
it was fun
It was really fun
Good, good. If we were in the same class, we were probably in the same group.
It's almost like I'm getting used to it
Like a circle
Ah, 01
It's 01
Karami
Nyoki Nyoki
Seriously huge
You know, you know.
Quite an older person
I feel the youngest this time
baby
Is it the best?
Yan-chan and I
You're a genius, aren't you?
it's over
everyone commented
It was amazing
thank you
me
very cute
Even though she's so thin, she seems to be able to eat rice.
What kind of rumor is that? Wait, that?
No, that's not what Maichi said.
Oh, I see, no.
Maichi eats, that's the story.
Oh, is that a secret?
Yeah, not at all
Oh, are you really saying that?
Maichi-san eat?
I eat a lot
Maichi-san eats a lot, right?
Haven't you eaten?
I'll eat some
That's great, but it's best that you stay healthy.
Oh no, I'm going
That's me too.
Yes, I see.
We were together, right?
I changed my name.
No, please.
it's okay.
We were social again.
I love it.
He told me he liked me before.
It's now.
Wow.
Please stop.
I like it.
It begins.
Someday.
Eh, that's cute.
cute!
congratulations
Feel free to take photos if you feel like it
cute
thank you
congratulations
Suzuki-chan wore my costume
I became Kanamin-san.
He made me wear panties
No, she's really cute this time
A little bit of Kisei-chan's check and it's all Kanamine part.
That kind of thing happens, right?
It's fate
I'm happy, thank you
Let's go, high cheese
Because I did a BTG song
This is exactly the trade
yes
I'll do Aoi-chan's part too.
I was sung by the chewing cam.
It's a BTG pose.
Which of these is gin?
This is chewing gum gum cloth
Oh, is that so?
I wonder if we're all G from BTG.
We were talking about whether it was G from Girls or something.
Actually chewing gum
Is it the G for chewing gum?
Then I'll tell everyone later.
please
Please do it. It was fun.
thank you
I'm going home
I did my best
thank you for your hard work
I did it
With the clothes I wore today
Mayama's role
Mayama's role?
only
Let me do it
Surprisingly, it's Patoi, isn't it?
Surprisingly good, right?
It's tough, thank you
Hiyorin's cute voice says my loud voice
Thank you for letting me vent
No way
cute
So cute indeed
I want to do it again for another year
When I found something,
Hello.
thank you.
Not at all.
Do you follow me a lot?
Uta warigasa,
It was fun.
I was really invited.
thank you.
That's not the case.
me too.
It's the highest grade.
thank you.
Yay!
It happened!
It was a flower birthday!
thank you!
Thank you!
cute!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
What do you want to eat?
Meat!
There's meat all over my clothes
Because it's all you can eat
Hey hey hey
I'm going somewhere
Also
It's a bit unpleasant
thank you
return to me
I will do my best
I did my best. She was a great singer and made my ears happy.
kind.
I listen to it all the time.
Hello, it's been a while.
I also watched it on YouTube.
I'm contributing to the world.
I have contributed about 100 times.
amazing.
Last, yes, Steese.
thank you for your hard work.
yes.
I'll enjoy having this.
The staff completed the park successfully.
Thank you everyone for your hard work!
Good luck everyone!
do your best!
Everyone is great!
Praise me more!
Alright!
Yay!
This time, all three days had completely different sections.
Each group forms a unit about other groups, etc.
Also, age, etc.
All of them are free idols,
MVCI
It's all sorts of things, I've danced to many different people's songs at Maisone.
I think that's why you were able to see things about us that you don't usually see.
I think so, but
Good luck everyone
Yes, you can also select it in the comment section.
I would like you to write more about what was good about it.
The whole staff is amazing
Everyone, everyone, including everyone.
really amazing
Thank you everyone for your hard work
At first, I was really confused, so I wonder what will happen next.
I did my best to support the staff and staff members who made it through.
Stapler is the best!
The best! The best!
Thank you everyone.
thank you very much.
It's not possible at all.
There were also lots of penlights.
Well, that's great.
It was amazing what saved me.
Thank you very much.
thank you very much.
Let's continue to do our best.
Will the next live show be Tamawari?
Hey! Tamawari!
As expected! It's finally here, everyone! There's fresh greenery! That's right!
See you soon! Let's do our best! We've got more tasks to do!
So from now on, I will continue to grow and do my best!
thank you very much!